Message from the King is a action, mystery, thriller
film directed by Fabrice Du Welz.
On a relentless quest to avenge his sister's murder, a man from Cape Town
infiltrates a sprawling network of lowlifes and elites in Los Angeles.
Jacob King, played by Chadwick Boseman.
Wentworth, played by Luke Evans.
Preston, played by Alfred Molina.
Kelly, played by Teresa Palmer.
Trish, played by Natalie Martinez.
Leary, played by Chris Mulkey.
Message from the King is a 2016 revenge-action-thriller film directed by
Fabrice Du Welz, and written by Stephen Cornwell and Oliver Butcher.
The film is produced by Cornwell, David Lancaster and Simon Cornwell and stars
Chadwick Boseman, Luke Evans, Teresa Palmer, and Alfred Molina.
The film's plot revolves around Jacob King (Boseman), a man from Cape Town, South Africa who travels to Los Angeles
in order to find his younger sister and, after finding out she is dead, he works to avenge her death.
The project was announced on November 4, 2014, along with Boseman's casting.
Principal photography began in February 2015 in Los Angeles, California.
Other filming locations included Cape Town, South
Africa, Glendale, Beverly Hills and Topanga.
The film premiered at the 2016 Toronto International
Film Festival on September 8, 2016.
It received mixed reviews from critics, with praise directed at Boseman's
performance and criticism aimed at the script and the overall pacing.
Netflix released the film on August 4, 2017.
The film explores themes of tattoo, morgue,
flashback, money, los angeles, california.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.